

Email souhila\_aouad@outlook.com Phone **+213 656861133** Linkedin linkedin.com/in/souhila-aouad-578073171/ Behance behance.net/souhilaad



## **SUMMARY**

a junior UX/UI Designer and developer who has a Google UX Design certificate with capacity of doing case studies which allow to have a good user experience also frontend developer who searchs for opportunites to improve her skills and having a strong carreer.



## **EXPERIENCE**

## USTHB / Dec 2020 - Sept 2021

#### A META-HEURISTIC APPROACH FOR THE OPTIMIZA-TION OF COVERAGE IN THE 5G NETWORK

- Coverage of a 5G network using the Atoll tool.
- · Use of GWO meta-heuristics to maximize cover.
- · Implementation of an application with Python and PyQt5 for optimize coverage.

GWO Python PyQt5 Atoll

#### LRIA - USTHB/ Dec 2018 - June 2019

#### "ABALONE" STRATEGY GAME

· Implementation of the MiniMAx and AlphaBeta algorithm. • Development of a heuristic for the game. • Image processing (color detection). • Play two computers in real time.

Java Processing OpenCv

Image Processing



Languages: Python, java, C++, C, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Tools: Figma, Adobe Xd, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Intellij, Visual Studio, Android Studio Processing, pyCharm, Blender, Git, Github, MongoDB, SQL.

Design: User research, Wireframing, Prototyping, Usability Studies, Presentation



# **PROJECTS**

- · Coffee Shop Mobile App Case study Figma.
- · Makeup tutorials Website Case study Adobe Xd.
- Book Mobile App Case study Figma.
- · Website E-Commerce Frontend.
- · Website to sell movie tickets -Javafx, php.



## **EDUCATION**

#### Master in Distributed Networks and Systems

Sept 2019 - Sept 2021

Houari Boumediene University of Science and Technology

# **Bachelor in Information Systems and Software Engineering**

Sept 2015 - July 2019

Houari Boumediene University of Science and Technology



# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- · Certificat de conception Google UX
- · Practical Web Development
- · Pixel Art for Video Games

### **LANGUAGES**

· Arabe: maternal.

· Frensh: advanced intermediate. • English: advanced intermediate.